

CAOIMHE YOUNG

Mandurah WA
0449800337
caoimhejyoti@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Caoimhe is a full stack web developer with experience in requirements gathering, data analysis and database governance with a passion for driving efficiencies and improving the way organisations work. Recently graduated from the She Codes Plus Program.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Junior Developer Matrix Data January 2024

- Part of a team developing a new database for a mining company.
- Responsible for the front end wireframes
- Responsible for user flow diagrams based on database ERD

School Officer

North Mandurah Primary School October 2023 - current

- Re-designing the school website:
 - $\circ\;$ re-mapping information flow to improve UX
 - school leadership consultation to ensure business needs are met
 - o self-taught WordPress web design
- Day-day operations of school administration:
 - stakeholder engagement, support and communication
 - $\circ \ \ \text{student first aid and medication management}$
 - o student data input and management

SKILLS

- Python, MySQL, jQuery, Sequelize, MongoDB, GraphQL, Slack, Django, Django Rest Framework, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Git, React, NodeJs, Apollo, Heroku, Fly.io, Netlify, GitHub Pages.
- Report writing/development, process mapping and project management.

School Officer

Warnbro Education Support Center August - December 2023

- Supporting the transfer from locally-hosted IMS to a cloud based system
 - Working with stakeholders to analyse business processes & their impact with new IMS
 - $\circ\,$ Focus on medical data governance & migration
- Day-day operations of school administration:
 - o stakeholder engagement, support & comms
 - o student medication management
 - o student data input and management
- Writing & managing two major grant applications.

Marketing Officer

Coastal Lakes College January 2022 to January 2023

- Manage all marketing, comms & events for a new high school in the Mandurah region.
- Managed college website expansion into senior school:
 - o self-taught web design and coding
 - website content copywriting
 - collaborated with external providers
- Expanded & designed all in-house documents resulting in easier access to information for stakeholders & the community.
- Established a college Instagram, increasing the college's web presence, broadening the audience.
- Negotiated funding for end of year awards, allowing an increase in award value and number.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE cont.

School Officer

Coastal Lakes College

August 2021 to January 2022

- Day-day operations of school administration:
 - stakeholder engagement, support and communication
 - o student first aid and medication management
 - student data input and management

Freelance Events and Theatre Technician

Perth Jan 2021 - August 2021

Worked at various events around the Perth region, including the Perth Fringe.

Accreditation Manager

Royal Horticultural Society, UK January 2019 to December 2019

Responsible for the access to five world-renowned flower shows; 42,000 individuals across the individual show sites.

- Pioneered the new Accreditation Manager role.
- Established operational processes allowing for a seamless transition into the Shows Department.
- Collaborated with external contractors to achieve smooth operation on site.
- Spearheaded the upgrade of data management software, including the designing of data storage and user experience.
- Supervised and trained all team members, enabling the continuation of company processes while on site.

EDUCATION

Plus Program

She Codes Australia Graduated April 2024

Fullstack Coding Bootcamp

University of Western Australia 2023

Bachelor of Arts in Choreography

Falmouth University, UK 2014

PROJECTS

Byte Time

https://bytetime.netlify.app/

https://github.com/SheCodesAus/2024 bit by bit fron tend

https://github.com/SheCodesAus/2024 bit by bit back end

Byte Time was created as part of the She Codes Plus Program. Byte Time is an app that facilitates the onboarding and management process of assigning users to an event based on availability and skill set.

Responsibilities

- · Git Manager
 - Supporting the group with all git actions and merge conflicts.
- · Front end engineer
 - o Coding front end logic.

Relevant Tools

- React JS
- Git
- Python/DRF

Out and About

https://outnabout.herokuapp.com

https://github.com/caoimhejyoti/out-and-about

Out and About is all about getting outdoors and seeing your local area. Users answer riddles, get quest maps and then go on an adventure. A key goal of this project was to encourage users to exercise and get moving without it being the focus.

Responsibilities

- Database model design
- Researching APIs, creating and rendering of maps.
- Creation of QR Code page and badge rendering
- Design of user reward badges
- Working as part of the team utilising Github projects to systematically resolve development issues.

Relevant Tools

- React JS
- Mapbox API
- Material UI library
- MongoDB/Mongoose
- Apollo/GraphQL

